<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on TireFire.dev</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on TireFire.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:38:46 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World</title><link>/posts/hello_world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:38:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>/posts/hello_world/</guid><description>My wife was remarking on how bad my current domain excellent.io is to spell when I set her up with an account for email. She has also recently started taking a C++ fundamentals class and asked how hard it would be to get a new domain that sounded more developer focused. Seeing as dumpsterfire.dev was already taken, I thought the next best word to describe tech is &amp;ldquo;tirefire&amp;rdquo;. Now my bank account is short $12 and I am the proud owner of tirefire.</description><content>&lt;p>My wife was remarking on how bad my current domain &lt;code>excellent.io&lt;/code> is to spell when I set her up with an account for email.
She has also recently started taking a C++ fundamentals class and asked how hard it would be to get a new domain that
sounded more developer focused. Seeing as &lt;code>dumpsterfire.dev&lt;/code> was already taken, I thought the next best word to describe
tech is &amp;ldquo;tirefire&amp;rdquo;. Now my bank account is short $12 and I am the proud owner of &lt;code>tirefire.dev&lt;/code>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Normally I&amp;rsquo;d buy a domain, set up my email, throw in a DNS redirect to my GitHub page and call it a day. However, I was
inspired by my wife&amp;rsquo;s willingness to step out of her comfort zone and try something new, so I decided to do the same.
I have read others blogs and benefited from their experience, but I&amp;rsquo;ve always been afraid to start one myself. Writing
has never been my greatest strength and the paralyzing fear of looking dumb on the internet for missing a comma or poor
grammar has always been a blocker.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As an engineer, I am always learning, and I don&amp;rsquo;t see why blogging needs to be any different. So, as is with any of the code
I write, PRs welcome on &lt;a href="https://github.com/elliott-davis/tirefire">GitHub&lt;/a> if you see any mistakes or want to do a guest
post about your own tirefires.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>